{
  "LevelId": 73,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 745,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "GRILLWORKS",
      "question": "precision-engineered grilling equipment known for its exceptional performance and durability"
    },
    {
      "id": 746,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CALCULATOR",
      "question": "mathematical computations and solving numerical problems,"
    },
    {
      "id": 747,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "DETOXICATE",
      "question": "process of removing harmful substances or toxins from the body"
    },
    {
      "id": 748,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BACTEREMIC",
      "question": "a condition characterized by the presence of bacteria in the bloodstream"
    },
    {
      "id": 749,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "TELEMARKED",
      "question": "phone calls from sales representatives trying to promote products or services"
    },
    {
      "id": 750,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CORNBREADS",
      "question": "savory bread, often associated with Southern cuisine, is made using cornmeal as a primary ingredient"
    },
    {
      "id": 751,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "ALVEOLARLY",
      "question": "breathing occur, specifically referring to the proper expansion"
    },
    {
      "id": 752,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "ENTERTAINS",
      "question": "talented host or performer do to engage, amuse, and captivate an audience"
    },
    {
      "id": 753,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "FIBERBOARD",
      "question": "construction and furniture, is made by compressing and molding wood fibers"
    },
    {
      "id": 754,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CAMPGROUND",
      "question": "outdoor enthusiasts typically set up tents or park RVs to enjoy the natural surroundings,"
    },
    {
      "id": 755,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "LUXEMBOURG",
      "question": "European country, known for its picturesque landscapes, medieval castles, and a blend of French,"
    }
  ]
}